'use strict'

const STORE = [
	{
		question: "What is known as Japanese horseradish?",
		answers: [
				"wasabi",
				"nigori",
				"mooli",
				"ninjin"
		],
		correctAnswer: "wasabi",
	},
	{
		question: "Which of these is the name for geoduck?",
		answers: [
				"hokkigai",
				"mirugai",
				"akagai",
				"tairagai"
		],
		correctAnswer: "mirugai"
	},
	{
		question: "What does \"sushi\" actually mean?",
		answers: [
				"raw fish",
				"sashimi",
				"rice with vinegar",
				"seaweed and rice"
		],
		correctAnswer: "rice with vinegar"
	},
	{
		question: "Which is not an egg?",
		answers: [
				"ikura",
				"tamago",
				"tobiko",
				"awabi"
		],
		correctAnswer: "awabi",
	},
	{
		question: "Besides water, what is the main ingredient in soy sauce?",
		answers: [
				"water",
				"wheat",
				"salt",
				"soybeans"
		],
		correctAnswer: "wheat"
	},
	{
		question: "Sushi is most closely associated with which Japanese city?",
		answers: [
				"Kyoto",
				"Tokyo",
				"Osaka",
				"Sapporo"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Tokyo"
	},
	{
		question: "Nori is: ",
		answers: [
				"green algae",
				"blue algae",
				"red algae",
				"brown algae"
		],
		correctAnswer: "red algae"
	},
	{
		question: "What part of the sea urchin (uni) is eaten?",
		answers: [
				"brain",
				"eggs",
				"gonads",
				"tongue"
		],
		correctAnswer: "gonads"
	},
	{
		question: "Which of these is not tuna?",
		answers: [
				"Skipjack",
				"Albacore",
				"Bluefin",
				"Hamachi"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Hamachi"
	},
	{
		question: "Who is often considered the \"world\'s greatest\" sushi chef?",
		answers: [
				"Daisuke Nakazawa",
				"Nobu Matsuhisa",
				"Jiro Ono",
				"Masaharu Morimoto"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Jiro Ono"
	}
]